we have here and it's that the bun
tenemos acá y es que la que el bollo se
has spoken out
ha pronunciado
[Music]
[Música]
the audiences of Sálvame with the new
las audiencias de sálvame con el nuevo
invention surprises me because
invento a mí me a mí me sorprende porque
really
realmente
and I am or rather that at the time the news and it
y estoy o sea que en su día la noticia y
was true or rather I didn't pull it out of my ass
era verdad o sea no me la saqué del culo
okay it was true at the time
vale era verdad en su momento
the workers of Sálvame it's an
los trabajadores de sálvame es un
open secret at Telecinco that Sálvame is
secreto a voces en telecinco que sálvame
always saying that they're going to close it down that they're
siempre están que lo van a cerrar que lo
going to close it down that they're going to remove it that they're
van a cerrar que lo van a quitar que lo
going to remove it but all the
van a quitar pero eso lo sabe toda la
people who work there know that or rather the people
gente que trabaja allí o sea la gente
in the hallways were already trembling and
por los pasillos ya estaba temblando y
now what do I do what the future will be like am I going to
ahora qué hago cuál va a ser el futuro
have that resume that I make I don't
voy a tener ese curriculum que hago no
know what happens that these people in
sé que lo que pasa que esta gente en
these companies work as if on a day to day basis or
estas empresas se trabaja como al día o
rather what is unknown suddenly I know what's
sea lo que no se sabe de repente sé lo
going to happen the following week maybe
que va a pasar la semana siguiente a lo
suddenly the audience goes up and
mejor de repente sube la audiencia y
a very strong topic comes out and suddenly a
sale un tema muy fuerte y de repente un
program that gives me serra support us land we put
programa que me da serra apoyanos tierra
out specials or suddenly they
lo sacamos especiales o de repente
change all the programming they had
cambian toda la programación que tenían
for the last week of the month and the house
para la última semana del mes y la casa
lives  like very up to date no then
viven como muy al día no entonces
really if it is on the table that
realmente si está sobre la mesa que el
Sálvame was going to close and suddenly it
sálvame se iba a cerrar y de repente
seems that they are closing all the
como que están cerrando todos los
programs except Sálvame I mean it's already
programas menos sálvame o sea él ya son
8 go suck it live life go [ __ ] yourself
las 8 a mamarla viva la vida a tomar por
and they put Sálvame watermelon it has
culo y te ponen sálvame sandía
been a failure
ha sido un fracaso
like a 10
o sea un 10
a 10 I
un 10
mean I'm not going to tell you that it's already 8 it
o sea no te voy a decir que ya son las 8
was impressive but man it's already
fuera impresionante pero hombre ya son
8 I think it was handling 11 and 12
las 8 yo creo que manejaba el 11 y el 12
which no it's not that it's impressive but you
que no no es que sea impresionante pero
're taking away from me the solution is this
me te estás quitando la solución es esta
and surely you're making more
y seguramente estás haciendo más
investment in this that determines
inversión en esto que determina
audiences
audiencias
at 8
a las 8
audience it's already 8
audiencia ya son las 8
where there could be the last day of
donde podría haber el último día de
them it's 8
ellas son las 8
the last day let's see what it says for example
el último día a ver qué pone por ejemplo
only 8 if the audience doesn't improve let's
ya solo 8 si no mejora la audiencia a
see if not over here that if the lyrics
ver si no por aquí que si la letra
currently it's already 8 it averages an 11
actualmente ya son las 8 promedia un 11
audience share
de cuota de pantalla
barely surpassing the million barrier
superando por poco la barrera del millón
with kisses
con besos
a 10 5 in a premiere or in other words in the debut let's
un 10 5 en un estreno o sea en el debut
see
a ver
[Music]
[Música]
a  day one day two days
un día un día dos días
and the most current
y el más actual
audience
audiencia
yesterday I'm
ayer
going to yesterday's hearings formulatv
voy a audiencias de ayer formulatv
okay
vale
audience nobody let's see if I see it
audiencia a nadie a ver si lo veo
flowers premiere to save me watermelon 10
flores estreno para salvarme sandía 10
but this to mabe yesterday
pero esto a mabe ayer
yesterday it's been two days no yesterday yesterday
ayer ya lleva dos días no
was 6
ayer fue 6
this is Monday
esto es lunes
these 5
estos 5
now we're going to see the 5
ahora vamos a ver el 5
the
el
55 the day 5 before yesterday okay
55 el día 5 antes de ayer vale
the letter
la letra
save me orange save me save me watermelon
sálvame naranja sálvame sálvame sandía
the same
lo mismo
and the same an equal
y a lo mismo un igual
then so removed
entonces tan quitado
so removed tank italy it's eight
tan quitado tank italia son las ocho
because I didn't raise them from eleven in 2013 and
porque no los subía del once el 2013 y
you're putting a save me that you're
te estás poniendo un sálvame que estás
expanding the save me
ampliando el sálvame
that in the debut it's being a failure
que en el debut está siendo un fracaso
the debut
el debut
that when you look more at the issue of
que cuando más se mira por el tema del
interest not the novelty to see how in
interés no la novedad para ver como en
the debut a failure is going to go
el debut un fracaso
down
va a bajar
that that goes in a week or two weeks
eso eso va en una semana o dos semanas
two weeks a lot in the next week around
dos semanas mucho en la semana que viene
there it will be 8 or 7
por ahí va a estar el 8 o el 7
complete failure
completo fracaso
[Music]
[Música]